All he wanted was an autograph.
The Fanatic is a crime, thriller film directed by Fred Durst.
A rabid film fan stalks his favorite action hero and destroys the star's life.
Moose, played by John Travolta.
Hunter Dunbar, played by Devon Sawa.
Leah, played by Ana Golja.
Slim, played by James Paxton.
Brenda, played by Jessica Uberuaga.
Luis, played by Luis Da Silva, Jr..
The Fanatic is a 2019 American psychological thriller
film directed and co-written by Fred Durst.
The film stars John Travolta, Devon Sawa, Ana
Golja, Jacob Grodnik and James Paxton.
The plot follows Moose, an autistic man who develops an unhealthy
obsession with his favorite actor, Hunter Dunbar, and stalks him.
The film was given a limited theatrical and VOD release, on August 30, 2019 by Quiver Distribution and Redbox
Entertainment, and received mainly negative reviews, with some praise for Travolta's performance.
The film explores themes of mentally disabled, autograph, fan, bully, murder.
The tone is intense.